{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "England",
                    "content": [
                        " Nairobi",
                        " Kingston",
                        " Washington D.C.",
                        " London"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Wales",
                    "content": [
                        " Wellington",
                        " Dublin",
                        " Cardiff",
                        " London"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Scotland",
                    "content": [
                        " Freetown",
                        " Edinburgh",
                        " Islamabad",
                        "  Singapour"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "USA",
                    "content": [
                        " Islamabad",
                        " Washington D.C.",
                        " Kigali",
                        "  Singapour"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Australia",
                    "content": [
                        " Islamabad",
                        " Canberra",
                        " Nassau",
                        " Nairobi"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Canada",
                    "content": [
                        " London",
                        " Bridgetown",
                        " Nassau",
                        " Ottawa"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Irland",
                    "content": [
                        "  Singapour",
                        " London",
                        " Dublin",
                        " Pretoria"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "India",
                    "content": [
                        " Pretoria",
                        " Bridgetown",
                        " New Dehli",
                        " Manila"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "New Zealand",
                    "content": [
                        " Dublin",
                        " London",
                        " Wellington",
                        " Canberra"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "South Africa",
                    "content": [
                        " Wellington",
                        " Kingston",
                        " Canberra",
                        " Pretoria"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Barabados",
                    "content": [
                        " Ottawa",
                        " Kigali",
                        " Bridgetown",
                        " Canberra"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Jamaica",
                    "content": [
                        " Pretoria",
                        " Kingston",
                        " Kigali",
                        " Nassau"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Singapour",
                    "content": [
                        " London",
                        "  Singapour",
                        " Wellington",
                        " New Dehli"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Sierra Leone",
                    "content": [
                        " Freetown",
                        " London",
                        " Canberra",
                        " Manila"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Pakistan",
                    "content": [
                        " Kingston",
                        " Yaounde",
                        " Islamabad",
                        " New Dehli"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Bahamas",
                    "content": [
                        " Bridgetown",
                        " Nassau",
                        " Freetown",
                        " Washington D.C."
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Cameroun",
                    "content": [
                        " Kingston",
                        " Yaounde",
                        " Cardiff",
                        " Bridgetown"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Guyana",
                    "content": [
                        " Manila",
                        " Cardiff",
                        " Georgetown",
                        " Washington D.C."
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Kenya",
                    "content": [
                        " Dublin",
                        " Washington D.C.",
                        " Cardiff",
                        " Nairobi"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Philippines",
                    "content": [
                        " Manila",
                        " Ottawa",
                        " Dublin",
                        " Pretoria"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Rwanda",
                    "content": [
                        " New Dehli",
                        " Kigali",
                        " Edinburgh",
                        " Canberra"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}